question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We Can&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
